<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>杂志在线</title>
  
  <subtitle>超高清，无水印，最快更新的杂志供你下载</subtitle>
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://yoursite.com/"/>
  <updated>2018-12-27T12:15:41.220Z</updated>
  <id>http://yoursite.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>eric</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>time usa</title>
    <link href="http://yoursite.com/2018/12/27/time-usa/"/>
    <id>http://yoursite.com/2018/12/27/time-usa/</id>
    <published>2018-12-27T12:14:17.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-12-27T12:15:41.220Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>TIME is an American weekly news magazine published in New York City. It was founded in 1923 and for decades dominated by Henry Luce, who built a highly profitable stable of magazines. A European edition (Time Europe, formerly known as Time Atlantic) is published in London and also covers the Middle East, Africa and, since 2003, Latin America. An Asian edition (Time Asia) is based in Hong Kong. The South Pacific edition, which covers Australia, New Zealand, and the Pacific Islands, is based in Sydney, Australia. In December 2008, Time discontinued publishing a Canadian advertiser edition.</p><p>《时代周刊》（Time）又称《时代》，创立于1923年，是半个世纪多以前最先出现的新闻周刊之一，特为新的日益增长的国际读者群开设一个了解全球新闻的窗口。《时代》是美国三大时事性周刊之一，内容广泛，对国际问题发表主张和对国际重大事件进行跟踪报道。<br>《时代》有美国主版、国际版，以及欧洲、亚洲和拉丁美洲版。欧洲版（Time Europe，旧称Time Atlantic）出版于伦敦，亦涵盖了中东、非洲和拉丁美洲的事件，亚洲版（Time Asia）出版于香港，南太平洋版出版于悉尼，涵盖了澳大利亚、新西兰太平洋群岛。</p><p><img src="https://hwzazhi.oss-cn-beijing.aliyuncs.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/Time-2018.jpg"></p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;TIME is an American weekly news magazine published in New York City. It was founded in 1923 and for decades dominated by Henry Luce, who 
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>nature</title>
    <link href="http://yoursite.com/2018/12/24/nature/"/>
    <id>http://yoursite.com/2018/12/24/nature/</id>
    <published>2018-12-24T12:11:27.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-12-24T12:13:46.540Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>《Nature》杂志1869年创刊于英国，是世界上最早的国际性科技期刊，涵盖生命科学、自然科学、临床医学、物理化学等领域。自成立以来，始终如一地报道和评论全球科技领域里最重要的突破，影响因子40.137（17年数据）。其办刊宗旨是“将科学发现的重要结果介绍给公众，让公众尽早知道全世界自然知识的每一…</p><p><img src="https://gss1.bdstatic.com/-vo3dSag_xI4khGkpoWK1HF6hhy/baike/c0%3Dbaike92%2C5%2C5%2C92%2C30/sign=91c51c8737292df583cea447dd583705/b219ebc4b74543a9870d236413178a82b9011407.jpg"></p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;《Nature》杂志1869年创刊于英国，是世界上最早的国际性科技期刊，涵盖生命科学、自然科学、临床医学、物理化学等领域。自成立以来，始终如一地报道和评论全球科技领域里最重要的突破，影响因子40.137（17年数据）。其办刊宗旨是“将科学发现的重要结果介绍给公众，让公众尽早
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>欢迎光临杂志在线</title>
    <link href="http://yoursite.com/2018/12/23/%E6%AC%A2%E8%BF%8E%E5%85%89%E4%B8%B4%E6%9D%82%E5%BF%97%E5%9C%A8%E7%BA%BF/"/>
    <id>http://yoursite.com/2018/12/23/欢迎光临杂志在线/</id>
    <published>2018-12-23T09:31:48.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-12-23T13:07:33.762Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Maxim magazine gives men what they want beautiful women and intense sex. See the world’s sexiest vixens. Learn how to make love like a gladiator. Stay up to date about the latest and greatest on all fronts sports, clothes, fitness and so much more! Maxim is sexy. It’s funny. It’s for real men only. And only Maxim brings you all the seriously sizzling pleasures guys enjoy!</p><p>《Maxim》杂志给了男人他们想要的美丽女人和强烈的性。看世界上最性感的女人。学习如何像角斗士一样做爱。在所有的前沿运动，衣服，健身和更多的方面保持最新的和最伟大的!格言是性感。这很有趣。这是给真正的男人的。只有马克西姆给你带来了所有男人享受的极度兴奋的快乐!</p><p><img src="https://hwzazhi.oss-cn-beijing.aliyuncs.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/Maxim_USA-2016.jpg" alt="123"></p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;Maxim magazine gives men what they want beautiful women and intense sex. See the world’s sexiest vixens. Learn how to make love like a gl
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
